hua tha very good morning friend or
relative banna kasana anonymous welcome you to ask
question oy drive only mission
possible egg possible to make possible gather we are
together 100MB withdraw questions for r
liberty subscribe now to change the first
question of the day
flash light on my screen as you can see
milk x you are travelling in forest road
with your friends during night time
when you notice animal crossing the road of
held him you will break and wait for the
animals to cross the said hangouts gather animal
switch hit lights S2 hai boond aur increase pet coffee peene ki questions as per al libi term review in hindi of force buddhi questions
aap log kare for forest
par apne friends raat ko aur aapne
dekha ke koi hai road kross karne to
aap uss time par the animal karo aadharik marenge tandav wait karenge
uss animal
ko cross hone ka ye hangouts kaide animal
aap horn baaj kar boon mil ko aur bhare denge iske woh
Run away, switch on the headlights to have been
you can increase your height to medium, that
means turn on the headlights to high GPS, by
increasing the speed you will leave
Suhaag way, there is a chance to Lipika this FTU
today and where you have a chance to be a
part of this and you can participate and when
vitamin E is born this is the first
question and for more questions to go and
you can participate in five of 5
and we take so much care of the situation you do
not always go to the jungle but if you are
travelling,
what will you do at that time, then just like this
is the mission regarding to make
roads and it is the responsibility to make
roads safer and try to change the situation of the
road is where can I request you to please join this along with
now school in
hello viewers every morning request you to
join in Hindi subscribe other staff
present to make a
bring change  In Indian everyday every Indian
must read this question bubble so you are
travelling roller for destroyer of rain
during night time when not in that
crossing the road rough and tough but doing
forest road at night with your friends
and you see that there is someone who is about to
cross the road or is doing it now what will you do at
that time bread and butter for the
animals to cross right away and you will add
that the animal is going to cross
its heart pure you will
scare it by blowing the horn so that it runs away from there
and pure lights to high beam
switch your headlights on five sides
or increase the speed of
your bicycle and go out from there
tom then you of the [ __ ] cycle you should
register your tears as soon as possible this question
in status for two days after dar
ram but maximum end with the
question educational reader so that you can
tell people according to the first question the district
president of every few can  Benefit
from Indian love you can win prizes and
subscribe family friends love you can also be
part of this campaign and also
like your contribution can be made our jo roz ko sab ...
He is Asif, so what will you do at
that time, you will put the bread and butter for the
animal, which is the cross breed, and you will
wait for that animal to cross from there,
hangouts are captive animals, now you will
scare that Anu Malik by blowing the horn, switch the
headlights to high beam, Rafi, which is your life
headlight, you will save him by
increasing your speed
and you will get out of there, so
please sign this to your answers in this
part of the customs, this will last for every one,
you can participate in the part,
we bring questions for every two hours,
every time a new question related
to road safety, you can enhance your skills
of wealth and prosperity, subscribe to us
and bring a new one with you
and that question changes, then
everything will last for you, subscribe
is our response and this rat, he is at
10:00 at night, please go in and check, he is
named after Vinod, whom we call Vinod Khanna.  I am
sure you will also see a part of 10th
that most of the war questions and I have screened that
you are travelling on forest road with
your friends during night time when you see
animal crossing then definitely you
will regret and wait for the animals which
cross based will put and you will wait for the animals to
come out
as per the hangouts you will blow the horn to save yourself from the scorching sun and
switch on the high beam off light and your
normal climb is to
increase your speed
and go out from there. Please
subscribe and subscribe the Channel on
road price
fuse and 1000 signs in chief follow all the
traffic rules regulations very important
meeting just this much
responsibility to make and
enemies of everyday sets more that if you are a big brother driving a car then it is your
responsibility to ask questions
and if someone is walking or cycling
or driving a common two-wheeler then on
fd these  Every individual has his own
responsibility and on or off tricks. The zones
you are driving in UP, all of them have their
own responsibilities.
If they follow their rules and
use their seat missions, then somewhere or the other
we can help in preventing these accidents
and we can do it only by helping each other.
You must have seen that when there is a
traffic jam, you end up with a bottleneck and some of them
go because of our stupidity and carelessness. They are in such a
hurry that they don't care about others
and we create such a
jam that a complete bottleneck is
created. Where it should take you half an hour, it takes
you two to two and a half hours
sometimes. In that jam,
you don't have to do a to-do list of things,
that's it. If everyone follows their responsibilities, then
somewhere or the other we will be able to
manage things very well. There is a
lot of traffic in Noida and we can control that
thing.  We can do this if we fulfill our
responsibilities well
Sholay Now you can see all my screen
which is our question but reader for you you are
burning one forest road with your
friends during night time when you know it's
annual crossing the road you head young man
you are driving through the forest at night
with your friends and you notice
that there is a diamond which is about to cross the road
what will you do at that time you will retweet for
the animal which will cross April and
wait for that animal to pass
or hangouts camera Nirmal you will
go and scare that army so that it
runs away from there switch on the headlight you have been you will
switch on the high BP
or you will increase your speed on I don't will get out of
there so
come as soon as possible and join us
register your answer we are
Amrit for now now I take leave from you thank you
so much for election * otherwise Kasana are you
on ark we should rise from information
possible gets together  We can use this, it's possible to
make and everyday say for some, thank you so much
after two years, are thank you, I will come and
join you when you ask, so thanks for
this, thank you so much